Instead of this Welcome to Stock Market Ka Money,
if you all are welcome to the Stock Market channel,
our second channel is English
Lover, if you have not yet liked, shared and subscribed to this channel, then
please like,
share and subscribe. So let's
start the video. On
May 9th, Erica went to hide about the company.
You can see your balance sheet
here. You will get to see March
21, March 2018 and March 19th.
If we talk about the reserve and surplus of the company, then
you can see that the
reserved surplus of the company,
which you can see from the reserve and surplus plus,
is more than 7600 in March 21, now you can see that it is more than 5200 in March 20,
whereas if you can see in March 29, there is
recharge and surplus of 5204 crores. If we
talk about debt, then
if we see the marks and what sequence,
how much gas is lying with the company. If we
talk about gas on 9th, then you can see
that it is of the city.  Squint you can see that what the
company has right now is
227 crores and
what was it at present before that, before that it was
4081 crores, after that it was 3236
crores, so if we cut this is the balance sheet of the company,
then you can see that the
shares held by the promoter, you will see
that it is
61.87, that is, the
promoter has, if we
talk about defense, then let's see it,
you
saw that if we
talk about 29.75, then you can see
that it is
11.68, if we
talk about public, then
you can see that
how many shareholders the public has right now, if we talk about that
6606824
base, then you can strengthen the rate i.e.
point
2102 any questions,
today we talked about ICICI Lombard
General Insurance, you can see, we are
talking about ICICI Lombard General Insurance, a lot of comments were coming
that you are seeing a decline,
subscribe
if we talk about it then next  Daily
appointment let's
talk about 30 grams of
subscriber
appointment let me tell you
that the biggest reason behind the fall in the stock is
that you have to buy obscenity through block deal
which is the company which
sold its stake in ICICI for 3.7 percent
so this has also happened and I
would like to tell you that you should think about this and
how many rupees will these people
earn from this and
it is being estimated that the youth will get
subscribed
so this is the reason and solution of the fall in this that
if
you invest in the market then such
incidents keep happening in the market but
you should keep an eye on these small incidents
and this is not a small company, it is a
company associated with ICICI Bank even for one percent so
you have to keep an eye on this company and this company
can give you very high returns in the future also
if we talk about another company then here in
Indian Railways if you continue in Indian Railways,
your shares have been running high and there is a
reason behind its running, there is a great reason,
you can see that today  In this, you will see that this
share has
fallen by more than 7.6 percent, almost
more than 300 solar points,
so let's talk about this company, so let's
see, the company has made profit for more than 18 years, let's
talk about one month,
so let's
subscribe for double six months,
you should subscribe, so
what is the reason behind this,
okay, the company had launched in the drain, you have got the
details of IRCTC, which is launching Darshan Torrent train,
which is starting from October 8,
and behind this, apart from this,
you can also see a lot of news
is coming on this, due to which you are getting to
see it, and there is another reason behind this,
you can see here that you need
500, which is the
normal train,
subscribe and you can also see that
this company had appointed
subscribe on October 19,
okay, the record is on October 19,
which is also the date, so this
company, IRCTC, you all
knew earlier that it will cross 5 thousand also
and this  Which can give you
abs and
returns on multi-multi through a report in this, if we talk about one thing then
you can see that this is the
subscribe button, if we
talk about one lesson then I am telling you that
those who have this city, please fold
and if we talk about railways, if we
talk about IRCTC then this share has also
reduced a lot and
if you want to make a new position in this city then
please wait, right now a new position can
prove fatal for you, so how much should you wait,
as soon as you get a chance you
can make this proposal, so let's
end the video, if you like the video then
please like, share and subscribe to the channel, if you have
not shared it with your friends then
please share me in the next video, till then
bye-bye